

# Evgenia Babulkova

# **Contact**

- +45 52 68 26 21
- ebabulkova@gmail.com
- evgeniababulkova.dk
- 💽 Viby J Aarhus, Denmark

# **Software**

#### **Adobe suite**

Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, XD

#### **Figma**

Mobile and web interfaces, prototyping

#### **Web Development**

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript

#### **CMS**

WordPress

## **Skills**

- User research
- Interaction and visual design
- · Wireframing and prototyping
- · Project management
- Creative writing

# Languages

Bulgarian (Native proficiency) English (Full professional proficiency) Spanish (Limited working proficiency)

## Courses

#### LinkedIn learning

- Essential training: HTML/CSS/JS
- What is Generative AI

#### Codecademy

- Learn JavaScript
- Introduction to UX & UI design

# **Hobbies**

Photography
Editing (Adobe Lightroom&Ps)
Music
Hiking
Reading
Extreme sports
Astronomy

## **About me**

I'm Evgenia, a UX/UI designer passionate about photography, visual organization, research and a bit of frontend.

I am well-organized with excellent attention to detail and a collaborative mindset. I enjoy putting together beautiful user-centered designs and am always curious about how I can improve, enhance my creative abilities and problem-solving skills.

# **Education**

#### Multimedia design - Business Academy Aarhus

2022 - Present

My focus in the program has been on UX/UI design, creating compelling visual experiences as well as understanding frontend development. I have become familiar with the design process and principles from the research and business side to the execution of a digital product.

- · Collaborating with clients due to the project-oriented curriculum
- Effectively communicating and presenting ideas digitally
- · User-oriented design, focus on UI and work with software

## Graphic design class -Emiliyan Stanev Secondary School

2017 - 2022

During my education, we had a lot of extracurricular events, that led to developing soft skills like empathy, decision-making, teamwork and contributed to my curiosity and drive to experiment.

- Organizational and teamwork skills
- Public speaking skills
- Creative writing skills

# **Work Experience**

### Cleaning Assistant - Bioclean | Arla foods

2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Taking care of cleanliness and putting in order office and kitchen areas
- Training new employees

Competencies achieved:

- Efficiency in regard to time management and organizational skills
- Collaborating on split shifts and communicating effectively potential problems
- · Training skills

#### Freelance - Photography

2020 - Present

# **ERASMUS+**

# Youth Finance Academy, Bucharest

2022

As part of this project, I gained an insight of how to structure and keep track of my finances through teambuilding and strategy games

# "Art is everywhere" project, Izmir

# **Voluntary work**

#### Charitable bazar

2021

Being one of the organizers of a charitable event for my teacher taught me how to lead a team into effectivelly organising events while complying with time and budget restrictions